onlinebootycall.com 2017-12-12

# onlinebootycall.com | Privacy Policy

This policy is effective as of March, 15, 2010.

MOBEZE, INC. ("MOBEZE") has created this privacy policy (the "Privacy Policy") as part of our commitment to helping our users better understand what information we collect about them and what we may do with that information. 

This policy describes our information gathering and dissemination practices for the website ONLINEBOOTYCALL.COM. By using or accessing ONLINEBOOTYCALL.COM, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy and you are consenting to have your personal data transferred to and processed in the United States. 

##  1\. Policy Regarding Minors 

ONLINEBOOTYCALL.COM AND/OR MOBEZE does not knowingly collect or solicit personal information from anyone under the age of 18, or knowingly allow such persons to register. If you are under 18, please do not attempt to register for ONLINEBOOTYCALL.COM or send any information about yourself to us, including your name, address, telephone number, or email address. No one under age 18 may provide any personal information to or on ONLINEBOOTYCALL.COM. In the event that we learn that we have collected personal information from a minor under age 18, we will delete that information as quickly as possible. If you believe that we might have any information from or about a minor under 18, please contact us at [support@onlinebootycall.com](mailto:support@onlinebootycall.com)

##  2\. Information We Collect 

When you visit ONLINEBOOTYCALL.COM you provide us with two types of information: personal information you knowingly choose to disclose that is collected by us and website use information collected by us as you interact with our website. 

When you register with ONLINEBOOTYCALL.COM, you provide us with certain personal information, such as your name, your email address, your telephone number, your address, your gender, and any other personal or preference information that you provide to us. 

When you enter ONLINEBOOTYCALL.COM, we collect your IP address, browser type, hardware profile and the address of the pages you request. In addition, we store certain information from your browser using "cookies." These small files are needed for the ONLINEBOOTYCALL.COM site to operate properly. If your browser is set to reject all cookies, the ONLINEBOOTYCALL.COM website will not function properly. 

When you use ONLINEBOOTYCALL.COM, you may set up your personal profile, send messages, and perform searches. We collect this information so that we can provide you the service and offer personalized features. We retain personal profile information indefinitely as long as you remain registered at ONLINEBOOTYCALL.COM. We retain information related to messages for 30 days. We do not retain any personally identifying information related to user searches. When you update any information, we usually keep a backup copy of the prior version for a reasonable period of time to enable reversion to the prior version of that information. 

You post user content on ONLINEBOOTYCALL.COM at your own risk. Although we attempt to limit access to ONLINEBOOTYCALL.COM members, no security measures are perfect or impenetrable. We cannot control the actions of other users, therefore, we cannot and do not guarantee that user content you post on the ONLINEBOOTYCALL.COM will not be viewed by unauthorized persons. We are not responsible for circumvention of any privacy settings or security measures contained on the ONLINEBOOTYCALL.COM. You understand and acknowledge that, even after removal, copies of user content may remain viewable in cached and archived pages or if other users have copied or stored it. 

If you choose to use our referral service to invite a friend to become a member of ONLINEBOOTYCALL.COM, we will ask you for information needed to send the invitation, such as your friend's email address. We will automatically send your friend a one-time email or instant message inviting him or her to become a member. ONLINEBOOTYCALL.COM stores this information to send this one-time invitation, to register a friend connection if your invitation is accepted, and to track the success of our referral program. Your friend may contact us at [support@onlinebootycall.com](mailto:support@onlinebootycall.com) to request that we remove this information from our database. 

##  3\. Use of Collected Information 

We use information in the files we maintain about you, and the other information we obtain from your current and past activities on ONLINEBOOTYCALL.COM to resolve disputes, troubleshoot problems and enforce our Terms and Conditions. At times, we may review the data of multiple members to identify problems or resolve disputes. 

When you register with ONLINEBOOTYCALL.COM, you create your own profile and privacy settings. Your profile information, as well as your name, email and photo, are displayed to other ONLINEBOOTYCALL.COM members. We may occasionally use your name and email address to send you notifications regarding new services offered by ONLINEBOOTYCALL.COM that we think you may find valuable. ONLINEBOOTYCALL.COM may also send you service-related announcements from time to time through the general operation of the service. Generally, you may opt out of such emails by updating your account settings under edit profile, sending a letter to MOBEZE INC., PO Box 880556, San Diego, CA, 92168 or by sending an email to [support@onlinebootycall.com](mailto:support@onlinebootycall.com), though ONLINEBOOTYCALL.COM reserves the right to send you notices about your account even if you opt out of all voluntary email notifications. 

Profile information is used by ONLINEBOOTYCALL.COM primarily to be presented back to and edited by you when you access the service and to be presented to other members. Profile information you submit to ONLINEBOOTYCALL.COM will be available to other members of ONLINEBOOTYCALL.COM. Your profile information and profile pictures will be available as search results. 

ONLINEBOOTYCALL.COM may use information in your profile to track trends in the membership population and collect information about the use of the website. We do this to improve our marketing and promotional efforts, to analyze ONLINEBOOTYCALL.COM usage, to improve our content and offerings, and customize ONLINEBOOTYCALL.COM's content, layout, and services. 

##  4\. Our Disclosure of Your Information 

Due to the regulatory environment in which we operate, we cannot ensure that all of your private communications and other personally identifiable information will never be disclosed in ways not otherwise described in this Privacy Policy. For example, we may be required to disclose information to the government, law enforcement agencies or third parties. Under certain circumstances, third parties may unlawfully intercept or access transmissions or private communications, or members may abuse or misuse your information that they collect from ONLINEBOOTYCALL.COM. Accordingly, although we use industry standard practices to protect your privacy, we do not promise, and you should not expect, that your personally identifiable information or private communications will always remain private. 

As a matter of policy, we do not sell or rent any personally identifiable information about you to any third party. However, the following describes some of the ways that your personally identifiable information may be used or disclosed. 

Financial Information. Under some circumstances we may require certain additional information, including but not limited to your credit card billing information. We use this information, including your name, address, and other information to bill you for use of ONLINEBOOTYCALL.COM products and services. By making a purchase, or engaging in any other kind of activity or transaction that uses financial information on ONLINEBOOTYCALL.COM, you consent to our providing of your financial information to our service providers and to such third parties as we determine necessary to support and process your activities and transactions, as well as to your credit card issuer. These third parties may include the credit card companies and banking institutions used to process and support your transaction or activity. 

Advertisers. We may use third-party advertising companies to serve ads on our behalf. These companies may employ cookies and action tags to measure advertising effectiveness. However, as a matter of policy, we do not disclose any personally identifiable information with third-party advertisers. 

Legal Requests. Though we make every effort to preserve user privacy, we may disclose information you provide if required to do so by law or if we have a good faith belief that disclosure is necessary to (1) comply with the law or with legal process served on us; (2) protect and defend our rights or property; (3) act in an emergency to protect someone's safety; or (4) as expressly provided herein. 

##  5\. Your Use of Other Members' Information 

Our services also include access to messaging services. As a member you have access to members' user names, and you might gain access to other contact information of other members through the regular use of ONLINEBOOTYCALL.COM. By accepting this Privacy Policy, you agree that, with respect to other members' personally identifiable information that you obtain through ONLINEBOOTYCALL.COM, ONLINEBOOTYCALL.COM hereby grants to you a license to use such information only for: (a) ONLINEBOOTYCALL.COM related communications that are not unsolicited commercial messages, and (b) any other purpose to which such member expressly agrees after complete disclosure of the purpose. Under no circumstances, except as defined in this Privacy Policy, may you disclose personally identifiable information about another member to any third party without MOBEZE's consent and the consent of such other member after adequate disclosure. 

##  6\. Links 

ONLINEBOOTYCALL.COM may contain links to other websites. We are of course not responsible for the privacy practices of other websites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site to read the privacy statements of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information. This Privacy Policy applies solely to information collected by ONLINEBOOTYCALL.COM. 

##  7\. Security 

ONLINEBOOTYCALL.COM takes appropriate precautions to protect our users' information. Your account information is located on a secured server behind a firewall. When you enter sensitive information (such as payment information), we encrypt that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL) and we store all payment information in an encrypted format. If you have any questions about ONLINEBOOTYCALL.COM security, please contact us at [support@onlinebootycall.com](mailto:support@onlinebootycall.com). 

##  8\. Notices and Revision 

We reserve the right to modify this Privacy Policy from time to time. Non-material changes and clarifications will take effect immediately, and material changes will take effect within 30 days of their posting on this site. If we make changes, we will post them and will indicate at the top of this page the policy's new effective date. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or through notice on our home page. Unless stated otherwise, our current privacy policy applies to all information that we have about you and your account. 

OBC and Booty Call are registered trademarks of Mobeze, Inc.
